DIGANTA SONOWAL

8812086203 - sdiganta321@gmail.com - www.linkedin.com/in/diganta-sonowal-aa8769328 - Moran Kushal Nagar, Moranhat, Dibrugarh, Assam, India

PROFILE

Proficient in Python Web development (both frontend and backend). Have worked on various web based applications. Also have a good knowledge of data analytics and Machine Learning, have worked on building ETL pipeline projects and visualization of data.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Science Intern (01/06/2020 - 13/07/2020)

Analytics Vidhya - Remote

Worked on various datasets by implementing data visualisation and Machine learning. Learned the data science and Machine learning using Python programming and also using python data science and machine learning libraries for data extraction and data transformation.

Guest Lecturer (13/02/2024 - 04/10/2024) Moran College - Moranhat

EDUCATION

St Joseph's Higher Secondary School (12/01/2002 - 20/05/2013)

Moranhat

Matriculation(HSLC)

Salt Brook Academy (10/06/2013 - 30/05/2015)

Dibrugarh

10+2(HS)

The Assam Kaziranga University (05/08/2017 - 11/08/2021)

Jorhat

Undergraduate BTech(CSE)

SKILLS

- Web Development/Web Design
- Communication skills
- Teamwork
- Data Analysis